

No. 209, Street 359, Derm Sleng village, Sangkat Chba Ompov II, Mean Chi District, Phnom Penh, Cambodia.

Tel: 081 338 668, Email: pisey.np@gmail.com

March 10, 2015

Dear Sir or Madam

I am writing to propose my candidacy for a position of Client Service Manager in your company.

I am enthusiastically applying for this position because I firmly believe that a combination of my natural ability, personality and work experience, all make me an ideal candidate for this role.

For the past several years I have been employed in a Worldwide Advertising Agency, Prakit FCB, now named as Draft Advertising Agency, where I found a bunch of experiences related to the advertising sector. After, I have experienced working familiar with Studio Production and Printing House for one year. Later on, I have joint Riverorchid Cambodia in December 2012 in the poisition of Account Manager and within one year period I was promoted to be a Senior Account Manager in March 2013 and currently, I am still working at Riverorchid Cambodia.

Additionally, I would like to state that I am keen to join a reputable and existing company like yours, where there will be a big stage for my talents. I consider myself as hard working with a solid work ethic to ensure all tasks given to me are completed on time and with standards.

Greater details of my accomplishments and achievements can be found in my attached resume. I am available for interview at anytime convenience to you.

Thank you for the time you have taken to consider my application, and I eagerly look forward to hearing from you.

Your sincerely,

Pisey Chea

No. 209, Street 359, Derm Sleng village, Sangkat Chba Ompov II, Mean Chi District, Phnom Penh, Cambodia. Tel: 081 338 668, Email: pisey.np@gmail.com

PERSONAL DATA:

Nationality : Cambodian

Gender : Male Marital Status : Married

Date of Birth : March 18, 1986
Place of Birth : Siem Reap province



QUALIFICATION:

2006-2010 : Bachelor's degree of Economy – Banking & Finance at

Norton University.

2007 : 3rd winner of English Writing Competition for accademic

year 2006-2007 in Norton University

Jul 2006 : Has successfully completed English Advance Level at

Newton Thilay Institute (Including four macro skills -

Reading, Writing, Listening and Speaking)

Jul 2005 : Has successfully completed New HEADWAY Upper-

Intermediate at Newton Thilay Institute.

2000-2006 : Graduated High School at Aknukwat High School, Phnom

Penh, Cambodia.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES:

Dec 2013 – to present : Was promoted as a Senior Account Manager at

Rivorchid, Cambodia.

Dec 2012 – 2013 : Account Manager at Riverorchid, Cambodia.

Duties:

- Report to account director
- Team management
- Communication Proposal Development (ATL & BTL)
- Make sure all job done ensure quality & meet client budget
- Understand client's business objective, target group & competitors
- Find strategy to increase sale & increase company revenue
- Develop existing business and create innovative technique to capture more clients
- Track monthly revenues and report to director on specified schedule

Feb – Nov 2012 : Marketing Manager at Neakporn Printing House

Duties:

- Take care existing client and seeking for new clients
- Propose effective materials Vs budget for client
- Deal contract with client
- Manage an effective timeline for client
- Make Report once the job is done



No. 209, Street 359, Derm Sleng village, Sangkat Chba Ompov II, Mean Chi District, Phnom Penh, Cambodia. Tel: 081 338 668, Email: pisey.np@gmail.com

Jan – Nov 2012 : Own a restaurant, Kongsey Restaurant on street 278

behind Lucky Supermarket (Sihanouk blvd.)

Feb 2011 – Feb 2012 : Marketing Manager at Idea Solution, Studio & Production

House

Duties:

• Business development Supervisor

Manage budget and timeline for client

Present & deal to client

Managing schedule & job responsibility for team

• Assistant Director for TVC production

2007 – Feb 2011 : Account Supervisor at Draft Advertising (Prakit FCB),

Thai Agency Company

Duties:

• Negotiate with client and carry message to team

Constructing proposal, budget and timeline for client

Managing the work of account executives

• Maintaining accurate reference documentation for internal management

Attending trade shows, exhibitions and events

• Activation & event management (Team Leader)

Conducting weekly reports to clients

Working closely with creative teams, copywriters, media team & 3rd party suppliers

Built Relationship and create trust with client

• Client Handled: Mfone, Hanami, Healthy Chef, Karat, Dcash, F&N, TOA, NIVEA, X.O Candy, LG Mobile, etc.

OTHER PROFICIENCIES:

Languages : English: Good in Four Macro Skills

(Reading, Writing, Listening and Speaking)

Thai: (Writing: Little, Listening: Medium, Spearking: Medium)

Khmer : (Mother tongue)

Computer : Microsoft Office (Microsoft Word, Excel & Power Point)

Internet & E-mail (Outlook Express)

Design (Adobe Photoshop CS5, Adobe Illustrator CS5)

Video & Sound cutting in Sony Vegas

Typing : 40 wpm for English

Driving License : Available

Interest : Reading, Watching new Movie, Watching TV, Listening

to Radio, Listening to Music & Playing Guitar.

REFERENCE:

Nong Andi Activation Manager at Riverorchid Cambodia Tel: 011 500 007

